It was clear.
Only one of us would survive.
And at the end it was me.
Not him.
Please, can you help me!
I've been kidnapped.
My name is Natascha Kampusch.
3096 Days.
This is my daughter.
Okay, Everyone.
We're not going to be this young again!
Cheers!
I love you.
Dad, we have to go, you promised
mommy you take me back by eight.
We'll go in a minute, my darling.
And then the man says:
…I've already got her!
Natascha!
Natascha, it's time to get up!
I'm not telling you again.
I put the dress out for you.
Do I have to wear it?
Have you got any idea how
long I've worked on that?
Other girl would be happy if their
mothers made them such nice dresses.
It's nice, but it makes me look fat.
Then don't eat so many biscuits.
What's taking you so long?
I've got to go to work!
He took to that bar again?
A child has no business in a bar.
If he brings you home late once more
It'll be the last time you go to see him.
Stop it! Leave me alone,
we weren't in the bar.
Pumpkin, I'm sorry!
Don't be like that...
Help!
Hello?
Hello!
Is there anybody there?
Get up!
Stand back.
Take off your shoes.
I want to go to my mommy...
Help!
Mommy...
Mommy?
Day 3.
And the prince...
the prince wanted to marry a princess.
But she had to be a real princess.
And the prince wanted to marry a princess.
One evening there was a
knock on the palace gates.
Go ahead, have one.
The aged Queen thought to herself,
we will put that to the test...
and place a pea at the bottom of the bed.
And she stacked twenty
mattresses on top of the pea
and then twenty blankets on top of them.
The next morning the princess
was asked how she had slept.
And she cried out: It was awful.
I was lying on something hard,
and now I'm black and Blue all over.
The prince then took her as his wife,
because now he knew he
had found his princess.
So.
The End.
Thank you...
Are you going?
Are you going far away?
Wait!
Will you give me a kiss goodnight?
My Mom always gives me
a goodnight kiss...
10 year old Natascha is still
missing, for the past week
several hundred police officers
have been scarring the area
since she vanished the
morning of the 2nd of March.
Despite their tireless efforts
search teams have still failed
to find any trace of her.
Natascha's mother has
been quoted as saying,
I have lost all hope.
How could you say that?
I didn't, Mother.
They write whatever they want.
The police diving unit
has also been used to
search several lakes
in the immediate area.
Thank God Natascha wasn't down there.
So far Natascha remains missing
without a trace... and now to sports...
"“Stop it, leave me alone...
Help! Help!"
One, two...
Pumpkin, I'm sorry!
Don't be like that...
Five, six.
One, two, three, four…
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three.
“I have to count the days.”
Four, five, six.
One, two, three... what time is it?
This should do you for next week.
Beef casserole and red cabbage.
Mashed peas and carrots.
You can have in one day,
and one in the next.
That should keep you
going till Wednesday.
All right.
And potato salad.
But with no mayonnaise
so you can warm it through.
Well I could even have
it with the red cabbage.
Like a vegetarian.
A vegetarian?
So... your favorite cold meat salad.
And lots of turnips and onions,
as you've always liked it.
But you have to eat it soon. Well let's
eat it now mother. The two of us.
What have you done now?
What makes you say that?
Fears are growing that Natascha
has been abducted.
Her kidnapper was probably hiding waiting
her to get to school shown here on the map.
Much of the information given by the...
So that pervert is sexually
abusing that child.
Why else would he ever abduct her?
Who knows?
Maybe he's crazy mother.
I wrote my parents so they don't worry.
Can you send it to them?
Take off your t-shirt.
Shampoo.
Not too much!
You have any idea how this stuff costs?
Good for nothing.
Then let me go.
Oh, nobody wants you.
My parents do want me.
Really?
Then why aren't they paying the ransom?
They don't care about you.
That's not true!
Really, well don't believe it then.
But nobody is paying anything for you.
They don't have money, why
didn't you pick a rich family?
Well your parents just
have to go to the bank?
That's all they have to do!
Every bank shows up money for kidnappings!
They don't care about you!
Because you're not worth it to them!
That's not true!
Yes, it is. Is true!
Come here!
Let's clean that hair.
Don't cry.
I said stop crying!
Would you stop?
Look at me.
Stop crying!
I can't stand whining!
Stop it.
Shut up! Shut up!
I can't stand tears!
Stop it!
The mess you made.
Look at me. Look at me!
You're gonna clean it all up.
Grandma...
Let's more coffee?
Well. I've had enough.
Mama?
Please.
Sorry.
You don't know why you
still can't get a job.
- What?
- I said, he still can't get a job!
Mother...
Sorry.
I was in the back garden.
- Good afternoon.
Are you the owner of this van?
Yep, what is it?
Can we have a look at it?
Yes...
What's this all about?
Would you mind open it, please Sir?
Oh I heard you were
looking for a white van?
Is it about that girl?
Natascha Kampusch?, Wasn't that her name?
Do you know anything about it?
I just heard the TV you were looking for
a white van with tinted windows.
So, I thought someone
might come by. You
wouldn't believe the
number we've looked at.
I can imagine, yes.
Why do you keep all your blinds down?
Is a habit.
So, can you open it, please?
Of course. Excuse me...
- I use it for work, building work.
What kind of work do you do?
Telecommunications. I am a technician.
And who do you work?
Sorry?
Who do you work for?
Siemens!
Well, I did.
At the moment I am unemployed...
So live here then.
I've got to ask you this.
Where were you on the 2nd of March?
Between 7 and 8 AM?
2nd of March?
On 2nd of March...
Oh yes, I was here. I was at home.
Can anyone provide you with an alibi?
No, I was alone.
So you live on your own then?
Yes.
My mother and grandmother
just visit me. Would
you like some coffee?,
we have some cake?
Thanks, no. We got to be going.
But...
- Bye.
What do you think?
It's all right
I love you...
Good Night Natascha...
Tuck up... sleep tight...
Good morning.
Is it morning?
How long am I gonna have to stay here?
Until your parents pay.
Can I have a clock? Please?
A clock?
If you're good.
Are you being good?
Did you send the letter to my parents?
Yes.
Stop looking.
What's that for?
So I can hear you upstairs.
And talk to you.
Are you alone up there too?
Day 183.
Good morning.
Hello.
Natascha, we have class until ten.
Please pay attention.
The Aar river, it has its
source in the Aar glacier.
Be quiet!
Flows through the Haslital valley
in Aar gorge,
As well as lake Bienzer and Turin
before transverse in Bern Midlands.
- How long is the Aar?
- 295 Kilometers.
- What was that?
That is correct.
Next is Aarestrup, Emil.
A Danish author close influenced by
the poetry of Heinrich Heine.
Heine, H. That's for later.
Miss Kampusch, how did you managed
to escape your kidnapper?
In the end I overpowered him.
How did you do that?
He was much bigger than you, wasn't he?
Yes, he...
I just overpowered him.
Did you brush your teeth before or
after you overpowered him?
What was that? Answer me!
Nothing. You scared me...
Did you brush your teeth?
Yes.
Did you rinse off your plate?
You have to obey me.
Obey me.
Yes, I will.
Obey me...
Obey me. Obey me!
Obey me!
Obey me! Obey me!
I have something on my arm.
It really hurts! Is so bad, you
have to take me to a doctor...
It's really bad!
If you're gonna play with your food
You don't need any.
You're too fat anyway.
HELP!
Nobody will find you.
You know where the shout goes!
Goes up to the roof. HELP!
No one can hear you or even can smell you.
They'll have to put
sniffer dogs on the roof!
Come here, come here,
I want to show you something. Come on!
Look, there.
See that? See that door?
Look.
No. No.
- No.
- Let me go...
Why would I do that after
Building you such a nice room?
Natascha, get...
"Next: “A propos" French.
A, P, R, O, P, O, S.
For: "In the context of
something”, “by the way ..."
“what we're talking about...”
“What I meant to say was...”
Are you there?
Please, I'm really hungry.
Please bring me something to eat.
I have so hungry. I'll be good.
Could you bring me some sugar?
Natascha really likes something to eat.
Please...
Say something.
Say something!
Please, I have to eat something!
I haven't eaten in four days!
Do you want me to die or anything?
Please, I have to eat something!
Anything!
Whatever it is, I'll eat it!
Just Anything!
Please!
I want to go home...
I want to be with mommy...
Obey me.
“Obey me.”
Obey me, obey me, obey me.
“Obey me, obey me, obey me.”
Obey me.
4 Years Later.
Obey me. “Obey me.”
Obey me.
“Obey me.”
“Obey me, obey me, obey me.”
Please...
Please bring me something to eat...
Please, I am obeying you...
Please...
Obey me.
I haven't eaten in three days.
Please, bring me something to eat...
“Obey me, obey me, obey me.”
Are you really that stupid?
You have to say “obey me”,
just as often I have to hear it.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
Do you hear me? I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please, just bring me something to eat...
A trial of former Yugoslav president
Slobodan Milosevic,
has begun the U.N. international criminal
tribunal in The Hague, Netherlands.
He is accused of crimes against humanity,
Charges he has rejected
pleading not guilty...
Heinrich Heine, poet and journalist.
Born in Dusseldorf
December the 13, 1797.
Day 1695.
Good morning.
Can you sow this? It seems undone
and they are so expensive.
Hey. Hey!
Why are you sitting there?
I have my period.
You...
You have your what?
My menses?
Already?
Oh great, that too.
Oh, this is disgusting!
This...
Look at that mess!
Clean it up!
I have to have a shower.
A shower? You just rinse it off!
Rinse it off! There!
There!
I 'em making even bigger mess!
What?
You better do what I say,
don't give me any lip! - Yes.
Wipe that smirk off your face!
Christ!
- You must have a shower. Upstairs.
- Upstairs?
Upstairs...
There isn't any upstairs.
Don't move until I call you.
And don't get any ideas either.
I hold the doors and
windows secured with
explosives, So if you
touch the wrong thing...
Boom!
Do you understand?
You can come up now.
You just do what I tell you to.
You'll go ahead of me.
If you scream...
I'll kill you.
What are you looking at?
No!
You want to touch my towels?
Wash it out!
You keep getting more hair.
Locking me up downstairs is not gonna
stop me from growing up... - What was that?
Drink up.
Then I can put that in the dishwasher too.
And don't turn it on until it's full?
Okay.
Right then.
I'm off.
Have you got a girlfriend?
Where do you get that idea?
Is she a blonde?
No...
No!
I'm glad.
Grandmother was beginning to
worry that you were gay.
Nonsense!
I know, son.
Wow, Christmas is upon us!
The year has flown by!
The shops are still open
for another three hours!
So go out and grab those last few presents!
Day 1837.
- Merry Christmas.
Stop, that's for later,
Look at this.
Oh, wow.
With screen.
Nice, hah?
Nice...
Ah, ah, ah.
Good. We'll see.
What… ah, again.
Merry Christmas.
- For me? - Yes.
- Thank you!
Stop!
Well, this...
All right.
Okay...
Watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it!
Yes...
Wow, a Walkman!
Now I can listen to music in the dark!
- Thank you!
- But you have to be good, 'cause...
we don't want the batteries
to die so quickly this time.
Of course, yeah. Thank you.
Keep going.
Jungle Book,
Treasure Island, Karl May.
Oh, wow...
Go on, read it.
The light of day is waning.
The hush of night is on its way.
So for the hearts craving.
Can pass just like the day.
This is so nice.
Thank you...
Stop that!
This... it's Christmas...
And I cannot stop thinking about it...
I really like to know how my family is.
You don't have a family anymore.
Do you understand? Because
I 'em your family! I'm
your father, I'm your mother,
I'm your grandmother!
I'm everything to you!
Because I've created you.
Your family is dead.
They're all dead.
But I'm here.
You're not Natascha anymore.
We need a new name for you.
An entirely new name.
Look. Maria maybe.
That's my grandmother's name?
Yes, sure.
It's my middle name...
Well that won't work then, because we
need an entirely new name for you,
let's find something else.
Look, Christa?
Viviana?
Well all right. Viviana, that's it.
So, hold it...
So as of today...
As of today your name is...
Viviana.
Let's say Vivi, that's better.
As of today your name is...
My name is Viviana.
No, your name is Vivi.
My name is Vivi.
And you can call me Wolfgang.
Well you could thank me.
Thank you, Wolfgang...
Don't look at me.
Look, what I knitted for her.
You will need something warm
when she comes back.
It should fit her.
Do you think she still likes pink?
I always took her to school...
in the car...
every day.
But that morning...
she just...
Why did it have to be her?
Take off your vest.
No need to wear it indoors.
What do you need all this space for?
Is your girlfriend moving in?
Can I have a shower?
You can sleep upstairs tonight.
With me.
No.
You got my sunscreen and lip balm?
- The energy bars are also there too.
- Good.
- Do you have your gloves?
- Yes.
A propos...
Will you take me with you sometime?
If you behave yourself, maybe.
I do behave myself.
Good.
If you're good, we'd be out having a
great time, Just the two of us, yeah?
So a propos...
Have you heard the one about the skier?
Just before the ski race begins,
an avalanche comes crashing down
and all the skiers have been killed.
So...
Go on.
So, the next morning...
one of the widows,
comes to identify her dead husband.
They open the first coffin,
and she shakes her head.
Then they open the second coffin,
she shakes her head again.
Then they open the third coffin,
and she nods: That's him.
Thank God, at least he came in third!
No. The other one.
I want to go out in the garden.
You want a what?
I'd like to go out in the garden, please.
You are just as tied to me as I am to you.
Day 2029.
Not so much!
Put the plate mats down first,
How many times do I have to tell you?
You don't need one.
Why do you have to do everything twice?
I mean you have seven years walking back
and forth all the time?
Hello, I 'em talking to you!
And I'm listening.
Go on!
And the oil is getting too hot.
Fish.
Come on. Even my mother
does it ten times faster.
What about something to drink?
Yeah.
Since when do you need panties?
Yes?
What are you brainless?
Put something down there!
Get those coasters.
You're worst than a dog!
A dog you can teach!
Go sit.
And don't think for a minute
you're gonna have any of this.
We need to change the filter.
Go on.
You can get through there.
- I can't.
- Yes you can. Go on.
- You need a plumber.
- No! I don't, and you know why?
Because of you I can't
let one into the house!
Go on, or there won't be any more water!
Keep moving.
That's it.
That's it. Go on!
Vivi?
Come on. Can't you take a joke?
No.
I went to three shops to find them.
Don't even think about it.
I've got my gun and I'll kill anyone.
Including you.
Are we clear?
I think my car is over there.
Lilac.
For the bedroom maybe.
Take one.
It will be enough for your room too.
- I couldn't find it.
- I'll show you. Come with me.
“Obey me, obey me.”
Employees in the electrical please.
It's extravagant for the bathroom,
I suppose, I like it though.
Vivi.
Go on. Go on.
Day 2175.
Come here, Vivi.
Come here.
Yeah...
Yeah.
Yes, it's very good.
Surprise!
Wow, lilac!
- Look. Hmm?
- Yeah, it's nice.
And see. All gold.
I know, I put the tiles in myself.
The Aphrodite bedroom.
Or do you like The Passion better?
Well, take a pick.
- I'd like to grow my hair back.
- So we go for Aphrodite.
Yes.
Oh, it's so nice.
And the carpet, so pretty.
The color...
You have good taste.
Well.
Plenty of room now for two...
Come on.
I've got a surprise.
- Now?
- Now!
I suppose everybody needs
somebody sometime, Am I right?
You are.
Now try it.
- That's very strong.
- Oh, don't be silly.
It's delicious.
I'm sure it will make me drunk.
You are so funny.
On a battling case in
Austria, it's been 6
years since Natascha
Kampusch was kidnapped.
On her way to school, there had
never been any real leads on the case.
I 'em here.
Many listeners will still recall
holding photos of the missing girl
splashed across the bridge and grass
during the first months of…
But I'm still alive...
As an ever riding theme for this book,
It's terrifying.
So many people disappear without a trace.
Why are you lying in bed in
the middle of the day?
Get up!
Aphrodite is here.
- Who?
- Aphrodite.
The bedroom suite.
Our wedding night.
This is very nice.
What?
- You do want to.
- No...
You belong to me, and I do
whatever I want with you.
Why did you pick me?
I saw your smile...
I saw your smile.
- Hello, sweetheart, are you all right?
- Natascha, no more biscuits.
How long did it take you to finish this?
From June to the following March.
The pipes and cables.
The plastering.
Always going to different
hardware stores to get things.
Getting rid of the earth
in different places.
Installing in the doors.
Ventilation.
All for you.
Don't look at me that way.
Stop looking at me!
What's that smell?
What are you up to?
Nothing.
You're not killing yourself,
you understand?
You will not kill yourself, you understand?
Look at me!
Ah!
You...
Will... not...
kill...
yourself!
Do you understand?
Why do you have to ruin everything?
It could be so nice.
But you ruin it.
Let me go...
Never.
Then one of us has to die.
18 blows to the head.
6 punches in the stomach
12 strokes in the ear.
4 kicks to the legs.
Go on. Go on!
Get up.
Don't act so helpless.
I can't...
Come on!
Go!
Oh, God!
My knees are so shaky.
You're going to ski!
How much do you think
all this stuff costs?
53 Euros.
- What?
- € 53!
Then go.
I'm gonna go.
All right.
Put on your sunglasses.
Hello?
Please, can you help me!
I've been kidnapped.
My name is Natascha Kampusch.
What happened in that toilet?
Nothing...
Don't lie to me.
An 18...
You want me to cut it?
What, aren't you hungry? Hmm?
Take a much bigger.
All right.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
A dress!
Put it on.
Here...
You want to dance?
Yes?
I am a good dancer.
God... you can't even dance.
Come here.
Slow, slow, wait, wait.
Hello!
Hello.
You're dumber than a dog!
I'm selling the van.
To have a bit of money.
Got to get it nice clean.
All right, vacuum it inside.
I want it completely clean.
The seats as well as the floor.
I'll do the windows. You won't,
'cause I just told you to vacuum.
The mags!
Oh...
Hello?
Yes.
It's about the Van.
Say. Hold a moment.
One second...
Right. Sorry...
Just a second.
No, not yet.
It is still for sale.
Uh, I think It had two previous owners.
Come tomorrow at two...
Hello? Hello, can you help me?
Please call the police!
What are you doing
in my garden?
Natascha Kampusch!
It's about a kidnapping!
Day 3096.
Right, stay where you are, please!
Is this the girl you phone me about?
- Yes.
- Do you have any form of identification?
- My name is Natascha Kampusch.
I was kidnapped eight years ago.
Hello?
Speaking...
Any news of him?
Mom...
- Here.
- Thank you.
It's okay.
Do not be afraid.
It was clear.
Only one of us would survive.
And at the end it was me.
Not him.
Vaultofplenty Subtitles.
Used Purplebelt timings.